在adapter的bindView方法中，
In the adaptor bindView method, we have to traverse the view
需要按照view的层次依次遍历来添加数据。
hierarchy to find all these different views to set data onto
即便是被回收的view，意味着view
them. If it's a recycled view, meaning that it was used
之前在列表中被用于显示其他数据，我们仍需遍历将其找出。
in the list previously to display other data, we still have
为了避免不必要的findBiewById调用，
to traverse and find out the views. To remove unnecessary find
我们可以使用View Holder模式。
View By ID calls, we can use the View Holder pattern.
当要处理一个包含不同类型view的列表布局时，
For a list item layout that contains different views, we can
我们可以创建View Holder对象。它的成员变量代表布局中的view。
create a View Holder object. It contains member variables that reference each
View Holder对象存储在view的tag域中。
view in the layout. The View Holder object is stored in
当该view下一次被回收并重复利用时
the tag field of the view. The next time that the view
我们可以立即获得需要的数据。
is recycled and used again. We can just immediately set the data
这时你就不需要在把所有的view遍历一遍了。
onto these fields. You don't have to go find all the views
这就是View Holder类。你可以随意给他起名字。
again. This is our View Holder class. You can name it anything
这货就是个普通的Java类。当确定了布局资源后，
you want, it's just a Java class. Given the list item layout,
我们执行一系列findViewById的操作。
we do all the find view by ID calls. That way, we
这样一来，我们就能获得所有子view的引用。在newView方法中，
can hold references to all the child views. In the newView method,
当我们加载了view之后，我们使用该view创建一个ViewHolder对象。
after we've inflated the view, we create a new View Holder object
然后将所创建的ViewHolder对象的引用作为view的tag属性。
from that view. Then we set the View Holder as the tag of
tag可以用于保存任何对象
the view. The tag can be used to store any object. But
但是别乱用tag，因为在读取tag的时候，你需要提前知道它所存储的是什么
don't abuse it, because when you read it back, you have to know
ViewHolder是使用tag的典型用法。
what you stored in there. A View Holder is a good use
然后在bindView方法中，我们可以使用tag
case for it. Then in the bindView method. We read from the tag,
来获得之前创建的ViewHolder对象。
to get back the View Holder object. And we immediately have references, to
然后我们能立即拿到所有所需的view的引用，比如图标View、
all the individual views we need to update, such as the Icon View,
日期View、描述View等等。来吧！动手创建一个ViewHolder类
the Date View, the Description View etc. Go ahead and define a View
然后优化你的adapter。当你运行程序的时候
Holder class and update your adapter to use it. When you compile and
你不会看到什么明显的变化。但是当你的列表
run, you may not see that noticeable of a difference. But now your
扩展到成百上千的规模的时候，它会比之前运行的更高效，体验更棒。
list will perform better when it scales to hundreds or thousands of items.